Dearborn, Frederick M. (Frederick Myers), b. 1876, collector. Frederick M. Dearborn collection of military and political Americana, Part II: The Civil War and the Confederacy, 1832-1915 (MS Am 1649.24): Guide.
Frederick M. Dearborn collection of military and political Americana, Part II: The Civil War and the Confederacy,
- Trenholm, George A. MS.L.s. to John Cabell Breckinridge; [n.p.] 20 Mar 1865., (960); 1s.(1p.)
- Trenholm, George A. MS.L.s. to [Jefferson Davis]; Richmond, 24 Jan 1865., (961); 1s.(2p.)
- Trenholm, George A. MS. (by secretary); [n.p.] 20 Dec 1864., (962); 1s.(2p.)
  Leaf from letter-book.
- Trimble, Isaac Ridgeway, 1802-1888. A.L.s. to [Pierre] Gustave Toutant Beauregard; Centreville, 4 Dec 1861., (963); 1s.(2p.)
- Trimble, Isaac Ridgeway, 1802-1888. A.L.s. to William Mansfield; Evansport, 4 Nov 1861., (964); 1s.(1p.)
- Triplete, Thornton. A.L.s. to Christopher Gustavus Memminger; Richmond, 17 Oct 1862., (965); 1s.(3p.)
- Tucker, A. L. A.L.s. to Simon Bolivar Buckner; Franklin, 12 Mar 1865., (966); 1s.(2p.)
- Tucker, William Feimster, 1827-1881. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; Okolona, Miss., 3 Feb 1872., (967); 1s.(1p.)
  - Reproduction of photograph portrait of William F. Tucker
  - Recto, letter
- Turner, M. P. MS.D.s.; Richmond, 1 Apr 1863., (968); 1s.(2p.)
- Twiggs, David Emanuel, 1790-1862. A.L.s. to [Jefferson Davis]; New Orleans, 10 Oct 1861., (969); 1s.(2p.)
- Twiggs, David Emanuel, 1790-1862. A.L.s. to Daniel Ruggles; New Orleans, 25 Dec 1861., (970); 1s.(1p.)
- Tyler, John. A.L.s. [John Henry] Winder; Richmond, Jan 1864., (971); 1s.(3p.)
- Tyler, Robert. 3 MS.D.s.:
  - [Richmond] 12 Dec 1861., (972); 1s.(1p.)
  - Same, 18 Dec 1861., (973); 1s.(1p.)
  - Same, 18 Dec 1861., (974); 1s.(1p.)
- Tyler, Robert Charles, 1833-1865. A.L.s. to Braxton Bragg; West Point, Ga., 3 Oct 1864., (975); 1s.(2p.)
- Tyler, Robert Charles, 1833-1865. A.L.s. to Gen. []; West Point, Ga., 8 Sep 1864., (976); 1s.(4p.)
- Vance, Robert B. A.L.s. to Maj. [Thomas M.] Jack; Shelbyville, 8 Mar 1863., (977); 1s.(1p.)
- Vance, Zebulon Baird, 1830-1894. 5 A.L.s. to [Jefferson] Davis:
  - Raleigh, 2 Feb 1863., (978); 1s.(4p.)
  - Same, 31 Mar 1863., (979); 6s.(7p.)
  - Same, 28 Aug 1863., (980); 1s.(2p.)
  - Same, 17 Mar 1864., (981); 9s.(9p.)
  - Same, 14 Oct 1864., (982); 1s.(2p.)
- Vance, Zebulon Baird, 1830-1894. A.L.s. Isaac Toucey; [Washington] 24 Feb 1859., (983); 1s.(1p.)
- Van Dorn, Earl, 1820-1863. A.L.s. to [Pierre Gustave Toutant] Beauregard; Union Mills, 4 Dec 1861., (984); 1s.(3p.)
- Van Dorn, Earl, 1820-1863. A.L.s. to Daniel Ruggles; Vicksburg, 22 Jul 1862., (985); 1s.(1p.)
- Villepigue, John Bordenave, 1830-1862. A.L.s. to Maj. M.M. Kimmel; near Hernando, 16 Sep 1862., (986); 1s.(1p.)
- Villepigue, John Bordenave, 1830-1862. Printed D. (unsigned); Granada, 9 Jun 1862., (987); 1s.(2p.)
- Vaughn, John Crawford, 1824-1875. 2 A.L.s. to Maj. J. Stoddard Johnston:
  - Rheatown, Tenn., 14 Oct 1864., (988); 1s.(2p.)
  - Bristol, Tenn., 5 Jan 1865., (989); 1s.(1p.)
- Vaughn, John Crawford, 1824-1875. A.L.s. to Jefferson Davis; Bristol, Tenn., 23 Jan 1865., (990); 1s.(3p.)
- Vaughn, Alfred Jefferson, 1830-1899. A.MS.s.; [n.p., n.d.], (991); 1s.(1p.)
- Wade, William B. A.L.s. to Maj. Thomas M. Jack; [n.p.] 14 Feb 1863., (992); 1s.(1p.)
- Walker, Henry Harrison, 1832-1912. 2 MS.L. (telegrams) to [Pierre Gustave Toutant] Beauregard:
  - Danville, 4 Apr 1865., (993); 1s.(1p.)
  - Same, 12 Apr 1865., (994); 1s.(2p.)
- Walker, Henry Harrison, 1832-1912. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; New York, 9 Jun 1871., (995); 1s.(3p.)
- Walker, Henry Harrison, 1832-1912. A.L.s. to [John Henry] Winder; [n.p.] 10 Jul 1863., (996); 1s.(2p.)
- Walker, James Alexander, 1832-1901. A.D.s.; [n.p.] 4 Feb 1863., (997); 1s.(2p.)
- Walker, John Grimes, 1835-1907. A.L.s. to Edmund Kirby Smith; near Alexandria, La., 30 May 1864., (998); 1s.(4p.)
- Walker, Leroy Pope, 1817-1884. MS.L.s. to Joseph Emerson Brown; Richmond, 7 Aug 1861., (999); 1s.(4p.)
- Walker, Leroy Pope, 1817-1884. A.L.s. to [Jefferson Davis]; Montgomery, 14 Apr 1864., (1000); 2s.(6p.)
- Walker, Leroy Pope, 1817-1884. MS.L.s. to G. Gantt; Richmond, 26 Jul 1861., (1001); 1s.(4p.)
- Walker, Leroy Pope, 1817-1884. MS.L.s. to John Letcher; Richmond, 1 Aug 1861., (1002); 1s.(2p.)
- Walker, Leroy Pope, 1817-1884. A.L.s. to []; Richmond, 18 Jul 1861., (1003); 1s.(1p.)
- Walker, Lucius Marshall, 1829-1863. A.L.s. to Thomas Lowndes Snead; [n.p.] 31 Aug 1863., (1004); 1s.(2p.)
- Walker, Lucius Marshall, 1829-1863. Printed D.s.; Corinth, 11 May 1862., (1005); 1s.(2p.)
- Walker, M. S. A.L s. to Jefferson Davis; Memphis, 17 Mar [18--]., (1006); 1s.(2p.)
- Walker, Reuban Lindsay, 1827-1890. A.L.s. to [] Perry; Saluda, Va., 12 Apr 1883., (1007); 1s.(1p.)
- Walker, William Henry Talbot, 1816-1864. A.L.s. to Gen.[]; near Dalton, 9 Jan 1864., (1008); 1s.(2p.)
- Walker, William Henry Talbot, 1816-1864. Endorsement s.; [n.p.] 24 Jul 1863., (1009); 1s.(3p.)
  Also endorsed by Marcellus Augustus Stovall.
- Wallace, W. S. A.L.s. to Col. John B.Sale; Malvern Hill, 11 Jun 1864., (1010); 1s.(2p.)
- Wallace, William Henry, 1827-1901. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; Union, S.C., 9 Oct 1873., (1011); 1s.(1p.)
- Ward, Thomas. MS.L.s. to [John Henry] Winder; Richmond, 21 Mar 1863., (1012); 1s.(2p.)
- Waring, J. Fred. A.L.s. to James Alexander Seddon; [n.p.] 23 Oct 1863., (1013); 1s.(1p.)
- Waterhouse, Richard, 1832-1876. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; San Augustine, 2 Oct 1874., (1014); 1s.(1p.)
- Waterhouse, Richard, 1832-1876. A.D.s.; San Augustine, [n.d.], (1015); 1s.(2p.)
- Watie, Stand, 1806-1871. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; [n.p., n.d.], (1016); 1s.(2p.)
- Watts, Thomas Hill, 1819-1892. 4 A.L.s. to [Jefferson Davis]:
  - Richmond, 25 Sep 1862., (1017); 1s.(1p.)
  - Montgomery, 27 Nov 1863., (1018); 1s.(4p.)
  - Same, 8 Mar 1864., (1019); 2s.(4p.)
  - [Same], 4 Jul 1864., (1020); 1s.(4p.)
- Watts, Thomas Hill, 1819-1892. A.L.s. to []; Montgomery, 29 Oct 1882., (1021); 1s.(1p.)
- Waul, Thomas Neville, 1813-1903. A.L.s. to Sterling Price; Shreveport, 3 Jun 1864., (1022); 1s.(2p.)
- Wayne, Henry Constantine, 1815-1883. A.L.s. to Capt. [] Bradford; Milledgeville, 13 Feb 1861., (1023); 1s.(2p.)
- Wayne, Henry Constantine, 1815-1883. A.L.s. to []; Milledgeville, 4 Jun 1861., (1024); 1s.(4p.)
- Weisiger, David Addison, 1818-1899. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; Petersburg, 17 Jun 1871., (1025); 1s.(1p.)
- Weisiger, David Addison, 1818-1899. MS.D.s.; [n.p.] 9 Sep 1864., (1026); 1s.(2p.)
- Wells, James Madison, 1808-1899. Cut autograph; [n.p., n.d.], (1027); 1s.(1p.)
- Wharton, Gabriel Colvin, 1824-1906. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; New River Depot, Va., 26 Jun 1873., (1028); 1s.(2p.)
- Wharton, John A. A.L.s. to [Leonidas] Polk; Nolensville, 12 Dec 1862., (1029); 1s.(1p.)
- Wheaton, John F. Printed D.s.; James Island, S.C., 2 Oct 1863., (1030); 1s.(3p.)
- Wheeler, Joseph, 1836-1906. A.L.s. to [Pierre] Gustave Toutant Beauregard; near Cook's Bridge, S.C., 10 Feb 1865., (1031); 1s.(2p.)
- Wheeler, Joseph, 1836-1906. 2 MS.L.s. to Braxton Bragg:
  - Tunnel Hill, Ga., 14 Feb 1864., (1032); 1s.(4p.)
  - [N.p.] 9 Feb 1865., (1033); 1s.(3p.)
- Wheeler, Joseph, 1836-1906. A.L.s. to Capt. Alb Ferrey; near Columbia, 17 Feb 1865., (1034); 1s.(2p.)
- Wheeler, Joseph, 1836-1906. A.L.s. to Col. John M. Otey; [n.p.] 15 Feb 1865., (1035); 1s.(2p.)
- Whitfield, John Wilkins, 1818-1879. Printed D.s.; Camp Arche Price, Ark., 15 Apr 1862., (1036); 1s.(2p.)
- Withers, William Temple. MS.D.s.; Vicksburg, 4 Jul 1863., (1037); 1s.(2p.)
- Whiting, William Henry Chase, 1824-1865. 2 A.L.s. to Braxton Bragg
  - Wilmington, 27 Mar 1864., (1038); 1s.(2p.)
  - Same, 27 Mar 1864., (1039); 1s.(4p.)
- Whiting, William Henry Chase, 1824-1865. 2 A.L.s. to [Jefferson Davis]:
  - [N.p.] 4 Feb 1862., (1040); 1s.(3p.)
  - Wilmington, 11 Dec 1863., (1041); 1s.(2p.)
- Whiting, William Henry Chase, 1824-1865. A.L.s. to Robert Edward Lee; Wilmington, 27 Jun 1864., (1042); 1s.(3p.)
- Whiting, William Henry Chase, 1824-1865. A.L.s. to John Henry Winder; [n.p.] 19 Aug 1863., (1043); 1s.(2p.)
- Whitfield, John Wilkins, 1818-1879. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; Vienna, Tex., 28 Dec 1873., (1044); 1s.(1p.)
- Whitford, John D. A.L.s. to [James Green] Martin; Goldsboro, 23 Sep 1862., (1045); 1s.(2p.)
- Whittle, William C. A.L.s. to Leonidas Polk; Columbus, 12 Dec 1861., (1046); 1s.(1p.)
- Wickham, William Carter, 1820-1888. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; Richmond, 12 Jun 1871., (1047); 1s.(2p.)
- Wickham, William Carter, 1820-1888. A.L.s. to [William] Smith; [n.p.] 20 May 1864., (1048); 1s.(3p.)
- Wigfall, Louis Trevant, 1816-1874. A.L.s. to Col. []; Washington, 20 Feb 1861., (1049); 1s.(4p.)
- Wilcox, Cadmus Marcellus, 1824-1890. A.L.s. to Samuel A. Christie; Washington, 24 Mar 1889., (1050); 1s.(3p.)
- Williams, John Stuart, 1818-1898. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; Mt. Sterling, Ky., 11 Dec 1871., (1051); 1s.(3p.)
- Williams, John Stuart, 1818-1898. Printed D.s.; near Tazwell, 23 Jul 1862., (1052); 1s.(1p.)
- Willis, Edward. A.L.s. to Capt. [] McNutt; Camp Allegany 1 Aug 1861., (1053); 1s.(1p.)
- Wilson, Claudius Charles, 1831-1864. A.L.s. to John F. Lawson; Savannah, 11 Oct 1860., (1054); 1s.(1p.)
- Wilson, Claudius Charles, 1831-1864. MS.D.s; Savannah, 5 Apr 1858., (1055); 1s.(2p.)
- Winder, John Henry, 1800-1865. A.L.s. to Braxton Bragg; Andersonville, 24 Jul 1864., (1056); 1s.(2p.)
- Winder, Charles Sydney, 1829-1862. A.L.s. to Capt. Allen J. Green; Morris Island, 13 Apr 1861., (1057); 1s.(3p.)
- Winder, John Henry, 1800-1865. A.L.s. to Col. John B. Sale; [n.p.] 2 Apr 1864., (1058); 1s.(3p.)
- Winder, John Henry, 1800-1865. A.L.s. to []; [n.p.] 24 Oct 1861., (1059); 1s. (1p.)
- Wise, Henry Alexander, 1806-1876. A.L.s. to Gen. A. Beckley; Big Sewell, 17 Sep 1861., (1060); 1s.(4p.)
- Wise, Henry Alexander, 1806-1876. A.L.s. to Jefferson Davis; [n.p.] 28 Aug 1861., (1061); 1s.(4p.)
- Wise, Henry Alexander, 1806-1876. A.L.s. to Arnold Elzey; Chaffin's Farm, 26 Jul 1863., (1062); 1s.(2p.)
- Withers, John. MS.D.s.; Richmond, 17 Jan 1863., (1063); 1s.(1p.)
- Withers, John. MS.D.s.; Richmond, 10 Sep 1861., (1064); 1s.(1p.)
- Withers, John. MS.D.s.; Richmond, 25 Nov 1862., (1065); 1s.(1p.)
- Wofford, William, 1824-1884. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; Cartersville, 4 May 1871., (1066); 1s.(1p.)
- Wood, John Taylor, 1830-1904. A.L.s. to [Jefferson Davis]; Mobile, 24 Feb 1863., (1067); 1s.(2p.)
- Wood, Sterling Alexander Martin, 1823-1891. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; [], 3 Jan 1872., (1068); 1s.(4p.)
  - p.1
  - pp.2-3
  - p.4
- Wright, Augustus R., 1813- A.L.s. to Braxton Bragg; Augusta, 15 Sep 1864., (1069); 1s.(3p.)
- Wright, Augustus R., 1813-. A.L.s. to Gen.[]; Augusta, 13 Sep 1864., (1070); 1s.(4p.)
- Wright, Augustus R., 1813-. A.L.s. to [Henry Constantine] Wayne; Atlanta, 3 Jun 1864., (1071); 1s.(2p.)
- Wright, Marcus Joseph, 1831-1922. MS.D.s.; Macon, 6 Aug 1864., (1072); 1s.(1p.)
- Yeatman, Henry L., Jr. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; Nashville, [n.d.], (1073); 1s.(2p.)
- York, Zebulon, 1819-1900. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; Union Point, La., 15 Jul 1872., (1074); 1s.(1p.)
- Young, Pierce Manning Butler, 1836-1896. MS.L. (telegram) to [Pierre] Gustave Toutant Beauregard; Prosperity Station, 13 Mar 1865., (1075); 1s. (2p.)
- Young, Pierce Manning Butler, 1836-1896. A.L.s. to [Pierce Gustave Toutant] Beauregard; Augusta, 31 Mar 1865., (1076); 1s.(2p.)
- Young, Pierce Manning Butler, 1836-1896. A.L.s. to Col. John B. Sale; Atlee's Station, 29 May 1864., (1077); 1s.(2p.)
- Young, William Hugh, 1838-1901. A.L.s. to Charles Colcock Jones; San Antonio, 21 Jul 1871., (1078); 1s.(2p.)
- Zollicoffer, Felix Kirk, 1812-1862. A.L.s. to Samuel Cooper; Knoxville, 7 Aug 1861., (1079); 1s.(3p.)